Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possessed powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends, Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Don't flatter yourself. The key to the Underworld isn't you, per se.
It's a magical channel known as the Tree of Kleefoth.
Dante revealed that creating the Tree of Kleefoth would require the use of both Dark Magic and World Tree Magic.
No more chit-chat. I'm taking you down here and now.
Meanwhile, all over the Heart Kingdom, the battles against Vanica's Dark Disciples raged off.
Through lightning magic, Karadus!
First, Luck defeated the skin magic user, Svengit. Next.
Food magic! Glutton's Banquet!
Down there!
Using the Mala method to give her food magic a boost, Charmy brought down Hoglet, wielder of hair magic.
The only way to get true beauty and strength is from a balanced diet!
What? Where did that enormous array come from?
I endured you so that I could take my time creating it.
True flame magic.
Crimson eruption!
Leopold, who had obtained true flame magic thanks to the Mono method, defeated the eye magic user named Sivwar.
If you're not tough enough to handle getting burned, then don't play with an Inferno!
Hisure and his nail magic were eliminated by the spirit guardian, Gaja.
You're finished here, Dark Disciple.
Oh!
Plant magic!
Magic Cannon Flower!
Serves you right for being creepy.
Queen Laura Pechka was confronted by tongue magic user, Robero.
And just his mimosa stopped him.
Yoo-hoo!
Happy to see me, little Laura Pechka?
I've gotta say, this is getting really dull.
With the Dark Triad out there on the offensive, it's been pretty quiet here.
Yeah. Oh, there is one thing.
I'm not sure if you heard this already, but apparently we may have a spy from the Clover Kingdom in our midst.
Don't be ridiculous! There's nobody stupid enough to try that!
You're right.
You there!
These are Lord Dante's quarters. You shouldn't be here.
Unless, you were that spy I've heard so much about.
What do you say you and I have a little chat downstairs?
What?
Where did you go?
Oh!
Oh...
傾向に埋もらえた人生の夢 Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder! Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it! Never give up!
限界を超えても 加速していく Experience! We cannot pay! Let's kill the whole!
Leave it myself!
衝動的に突き進め Don't be afraid!
誰よりも高く飛べ Take it to the sky!
想像を超えた世界をこの手に The ground up!
想像せよ 偽りどない一連の道 Yes!
It's the ground up! Hey yeah! Believe in myself! Hey yeah! Believe in yourself! Hey yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! It's my time!
There's my Loropechka.
Oh, there's no reason for you girls to be so guarded.
She and I go way back.
I only cursed you last time because Megicula said to.
Anyway, this should be a fun visit.
She's possessed by Megicula.
That must mean she's Vanica of the Dark Triad.
She's the one who killed my mother.
If it's just me or after, then why attack Heart?
You didn't have to get innocent people involved in all this chaos.
Oh, it's simple, really.
I knew that would make you want to fight me even more.
She's Heartless.
Well, you'd better be prepared to deal with us because we wiped out your minions.
You're the only one left.
Yeah, so you defeated all of them.
Oh, boy.
That sure was a great warm-up.
What?
My magic should have rendered him unconscious.
I don't think I'll ever be able to thank you enough, Lady Vanica.
Because of you, I feel never-ending pleasure.
Shut up already.
Take care of these annoying little bugs so I can be alone with Laura Pichka.
I forgive you.
Please step on me more, Lady Vanica.
See that?
Thanks to the curse I put on them,
no matter how many times you kill them, they just won't die.
Where do you think you're going?
You're still alive?
Of course.
We've only just begun trampling your poor little kingdom.
Long live Lady Vanica.
So the rest of them.
That's the power of love.
All hail Lady Vanica.
You little rat!
How dare you make me suffer the first pain of my life!
After I was hand-selected by Lady Vanica herself!
I am a woman of beauty.
I should never have been put through such a disgraceful ordeal as that.
And so, with the eternal gorgeousness given to me by Lady Vanica,
I shall destroy everything!
Why does it take them so long to do their dumb speeches?
Okay, bring our round two!
As I told you, you will be stopped.
Sorry, but unless you defeat me, they'll keep coming back to life forever.
And they won't lay off until your whole kingdom is dead.
So you are ready to play!
Took long enough.
Lord Petchka, let's go!
Right!
Noel, that's our cue!
Let's do it!
Water creation magic!
Valkyrie armor!
We're going to take you down!
Water creation magic!
Sea dragon roar!
Log magic, red beast!
That's your best technique?
It's just a worm.
Just let me play with you!
I promise it'll be lots of fun!
I snuck in a few seeds for my magic controlling weeds when I threw that last attack at you!
So I can't move.
But then again, neither can you!
Mimosa!
Leave the toad to me!
You guys focus on taking down the devil-possessed one!
The devil's the best one!
Oh, Lady Vandica, both of your magic abilities are great!
Curse warning and blood magic!
It's just like Laura Petchka told us before!
Laura Petchka!
Anyone home?
Oh yes, hello!
I'm here!
Apologies, everyone!
I was checking on something!
Seriously?
Because it looked like you were spacing out!
Now what was that about, Spade?
Right, I was just getting to that!
Each member of the Dark Triad has a combination of two different magic attributes.
Their own, and the one their devil has.
When it comes to Vandica, I've fought her and Megicula before, so I will come up with a perfect strategy.
We'll train with that in mind.
Nice fun, Laura Petchka!
I wonder if Dante and Xenon are having as much fun as me?
No, whatever those two are doing, this is ten times better!
Because Laura Petchka's here!
And I can kill her if I want to!
Sorry, that won't be happening today.
Because I'm here too.
I guess it'd be cool to have Dark Magic and World 3 Magic.
But if you ask me, it sounds like it'd be too much of a pain to drag those two back alive!
Wait, Dark Magic?
What do you mean by dragging them back?
What are you guys plotting?
Tell me now!
Do you honestly believe I'm going to tell you anything?
Shh!
World tree magic.
Dark magic.
The Queen of the Heart Kingdom inherits the previous Queen's powers, as well as their knowledge and experiences.
Here, inside Laura Petchka's mind, is where that colossal mountain of information materializes.
It is because of this place that the Queen is called the All-Knowing Priestess.
It's so... cruel.
Laura Petchka!
Listen, Noelle.
If we let the Dark Triad have their way...
They're going to open the door to the Underworld and release the Devils, killing more than 90% of the people on this continent.
And the world will end.
But that's insane!
It's so... cruel.
Laura Petchka!
How can you do something like this?
So many people will die!
Yes, but the ones left behind will be strong and my blood will boil along with theirs.
What's the big deal if the weaker ones die off?
Anyway, forget about the future. Let's enjoy them now!
Enough!
We can't allow monsters like you to roam free in this land.
Which is why we will defeat you once and for all.
The fate of existence itself is in our hands.
Mana zone plus mana method.
Water spirit magic.
Voodik sanctuary.
With this technique, your blood magic's efficacy will be cut in half.
Noelle's water-based attacks will increase in power.
Stronger. I need to be stronger.
What now?
The lighter your armor is, the more easily you can become one with the water.
This should also help you move more fluidly.
You'll be swifter than ever before.
Valkyrie armor!
Mermaid form!
You've destroyed so much!
But the damage stops right here and now!
It's...
Well, just look at you!
It's so cute, the little Laura Petch can't find a body!
This will be double the fuck for me!
Try not to die too fast!
Devil power!
50% strength!
Her blood can't harden as easily.
But that's not slowing her down!
I knew it!
We can't win with normal attacks!
Noelle!
Alright, now things are getting real!
51%!
She only went up by 1%, but she's so much stronger!
All you think about is satisfying your own twisted desires!
52%!
You don't even think about the people you've hurt!
You killed my mother, Asir Silva, the Clover Kingdom!
53%!
Yeah, who's that?
Talking about the past is pointless and boring!
Let's enjoy the moment, shall we?
I wish you'd give up and take your licks already, pretty girl.
Thanks to Lady Venica, we're never gonna die, remember?
We've trained so hard.
Trust me, there's no way we'll be defeated by the likes of you!
Not just for the world.
Not just to avenge the death of my mother!
You really are incredible, Lorpechka!
With your help, our magic will be unstoppable!
Yeah, sure.
I guess you had something to do with it.
Well, what did you expect?
Lorpechka's that amazing!
Oh no, not at all!
I'm not special!
Forget the modesty, it comes off as fake.
But I'm only this capable because I inherited all of my abilities and mana from the queens who ruled the Heart Kingdom before me!
Even so, your powers are unbelievably great!
They can't be inherited by just anyone, dear.
Because I'm so clumsy and goofy, I can't help but wonder to myself sometimes,
am I really worthy of the crown I wear?
Last time, when I fought Vanica and the Devil Magikula, I was scared.
And because of that, I was cursed.
I'm unfit to be a queen.
But when I'm with you, I forget about my status and things like that.
I feel like I can be honest.
I wonder why.
What I'm about to tell you will probably make me seem even more undeserving.
But...
I'm so afraid!
I don't want to die!
As the queen, I'm supposed to be so much stronger and more responsible!
I...
I do apologize.
A queen should never cry in front of others.
Oh, come on.
That's not true at all.
It's okay for you to cry, especially with friends.
Exactly.
Thank you, Noelle.
Mimosa.
How did you trip with both of us holding you?
No matter what, we're going to win this fight!
For Laura Pechka!
For our precious friend!
We're at 65%!
66%!
67%!
Are you ready for the big one?
Here we go!
You get my best!
Lucky you!
Here's 78% power!
Do it, Noelle!
We were waiting for this.
We need Banika to use the highest percentage of devil power that she can muster.
As her blood magic ramps up, she'll lose more and more blood and deplete her mana.
That's when she'll start drawing on Magikula's power to keep on fighting.
After that, we should be able to go head-to-head with her.
And when she runs out of that as well, it'll be time to use our ace in the hole.
That's you, our arcane stage fighter!
NERO!
With NERO's arcane stage spells, and your combative spirit and fighting style.
If we train hard and create a formidable team, I am confident with our abilities combined,
we can overpower Banika and Magikula when the time finally comes to battle with them.
Well, Nero, can we count you in too?
I'm about to seal away that devil's power you seem so proud of!
Mana method!
Sealing magic!
Eternal prison!
I won't let Queen Laura Petschka or this world be harmed by scum like you!
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful
夜明け前の空 静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
胸にしまい込んだままの想いを解き放って
その翼を広げて
One more time
今飛び立て
あの海原を見下ろして
誰よりも遠く 何度でも Will you fly?
Beautiful どんな景色も 君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
And never let go 僕のこの手を 離さないで どこまでも ついてきてほしい
The world is so beautiful
The previous queen's powers as well as their knowledge and experiences
Here inside Laura Petchka's mind is where that colossal mountain of information materializes
This isn't the right one
Not in here
Nope, no good
No
No!
Oh, darn it!
Why were the previous queens so disorganized, huh?
They could've at least put things in ABC order!
You're no better
No matter how strong the enemy or how dire the situation
We will never give up
We'll keep pushing past our limits
That's what the Black Fools do
Black Clover, page 166
Captain Yami Sukihiro